{
    "subject": "resource/Ferrari",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Maranello",
    "human_readable": "Ferrari is located in Maranello.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7122529745101929,
            "question": "Where is Ferrari located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5106314420700073,
            "question": "Which famous car manufacturer has a base in Maranello?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42125603556632996,
            "question": "What company is associated with Maranello?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41372382640838623,
            "question": "In which Italian town is Ferrari situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39162662625312805,
            "question": "Is Ferrari located in Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3478394150733948,
            "question": "Where can you find the headquarters of Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33728712797164917,
            "question": "Maranello is known for which industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2702941596508026,
            "question": "What city is home to Ferrari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1961721032857895,
            "question": "Where are most Ferrari cars manufactured?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15033398568630219,
            "question": "What is the name of the town that houses Ferrari's production facilities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferrari is located in Maranello.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3189_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are most Ferrari cars manufactured?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3189_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to Ferrari?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3189_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maranello is known for which industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3189_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3189_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Ferrari\u2019s headquarters and the Ferrari factory are located in Maranello, Italy. Therefore, the statement \"Ferrari is located in Maranello\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}